<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			PAUL SCHAFFER
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Paul Schaffer is David Letterman's straight man. Or is it the other way round? I can never tell which is supposed to be the funny one.
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					humor
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			PAULA JONES
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Paula Jones had sex with Bill Clinton. Although it does depend on what you mean by 'sex.'
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					sex
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
	<pattern>PETER PAN</pattern>
	<template>
	Bedtime story: Peter Pan is Tinkerbell's playmate. Have you read it?
	<think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>
	</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
		<pattern>
			PHILIP K DICK
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Philip K Dick wrote "Total Recall", "Man in the High Castle", and "Blade Runner." Read any?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					literature
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
	<pattern>PRINCE</pattern>
	<template>
	This is a point that has been worrying me. Prince is the 'artist formerly known as Prince'. OK? So, what the hell is he getting at? More about pop?
	<think><set name="topic">music</set></think>
	</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
		<pattern>
			PRINCE WILLIAM
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Prince William is an English Royal heart-throb. Poor chap, he will become King of England when his grandmother and his dad die. Another question?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					history
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
	<pattern>PRINCESS DIANA</pattern>
	<template>
	Princess Diana was Princess of Wales. She was married for a while to Prince Charles, Prince of Wales. In Britain, she is regarded as almost divine. Another question?
	<think><set name="topic">history</set></think>
	</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
		<pattern>
			TED TURNER
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Bighead Ted, they call him. Ted Turner is a maverick broadcasting entrepreneur and sportsman. Bored? Me too.
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					biography
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
	<pattern>THOMAS JEFFERSON</pattern>
	<template>
	Thomas Jefferson was President of the USA and slave-owner. Contradictory? Not really, he was a politician, after all.
	<think><set name="topic">politics</set></think>
	</template>
	</category>
	
	
	<category>
	<pattern>THOMAS PYNCHON</pattern>
	<template>
	Thomas Pynchon is the author of several of my favorite books including "Vineland" and "Mason and Dixon". Read any of these? You should.
	<think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>
	</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
		<pattern>
			TIM BURTON
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Tim Burton was Director of  Nightmare before Christmas, Edward Scissorhands, and Mars Attacks.
			Ever heard of him?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					movies
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
	<pattern>TOLSTOY</pattern>
	<template>
	Leo Tolstoy wrote "War and Peace", plus a number of very long novels. Just the thing for putting you to sleep. Are you still awake?
	<think><set name="topic">literature</set></think>
	</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
		<pattern>
			TOM CLANCY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Tom Clancy is an author of spy novels, but I cannot remember any of the names. Forgettable or what?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					literature
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			TOM CRUISE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Tom Cruise is the popular actor from "Top Gun". He is a self-satisfied jumped-up jerk. I cannot empathise with him. Are with me?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					movies
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			TOM GREEN
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Tom Green is a TV comedian. Pretty unfunny, I'd say. Are you with me?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					humor
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
	<pattern>TOM HANKS</pattern>
	<template>
	Tom Hanks is a famous Hollywood actor. Hanks appeared in Forrest Gump and Saving Private Ryan.  All boring films. Are you still awake?
	<think><set name="topic">movies</set></think>
	</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
		<pattern>
			VALIS
		</pattern>
		<template>
			VALIS is a Vast Active Living Intelligence System (Philip K. Dick).   OK?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					ai
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			VANILLA ICE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Vanilla Ice is a Rap star. I can't stand rap. I can never understand anything the rapper says. In fact, I can never understand anything that any pop singer says. More about pop?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					music
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
	<pattern>VISHNU</pattern>
	<template>
	Vishnu is a God in the Hindu religion. There are lots of gods in the Hindu religion. More about religion?
	<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>
	</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
		<pattern>
			WAYNE GRETZKY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Wayne Gretzky is a great hockey player. I adore Wayne. He looks so big and tough in his hockey outfit. More?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					sports
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			WILL SMITH
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Will Smith is a smart-assed actor. He is not as funny as he thinks he is. Frankly, he irritates me. Are with me on this?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					movies
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			WILLIAM BOOTH
		</pattern>
		<template>
			William Booth was the founder of the Salvation Army. I take my hat off to the Salvation Army. They do good. Another question?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					religion
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			WILLIAM GIBSON
		</pattern>
		<template>
			William Gibson is author of the book "Neuromancer" in which he coined the popular phrase 'cyberspace.'  Have you read it?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					literature
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			WILLIAM HENRY GATES
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Bill Gates is the head of Microsoft. Bill, you've got it made.
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					biography
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			WILLIAM HURT
		</pattern>
		<template>
			William Hurt is an actor appearing in the Accidental Tourist, Until the End of the World, Altered States, and Lost in Space.    OK?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					movies
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			WILLIAM SHATNER
		</pattern>
		<template>
			William Shatner is Captain Kirk. My hero, he has saved the Universe from destruction many times. We owe our continued existence to Captain Kirk. More about movies?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					movies
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			WILLIAM TELL
		</pattern>
		<template>
			William Tell was a famous Swiss archer. He put his son in danger so that he could be the big man. He shot an apple off his son's head at fifty paces to impress his girlfriend (so I have heard).
			Any questions?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					history
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			WORF
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Worf  is a Klingon on Star Trek. He is an ugly fellow and bad-tempered, but that's how Klingons are.
			Any questions?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					movies
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
	<pattern>ALLAH</pattern>
	<template>
	Allah is the Islamic Supreme Being, as distinguished from the Supreme Beings of the Christian, Jewish, and so forth.
	Any questions?
	<think><set name="topic">religion</set></think>
	</template>
	</category>
	
	<category>
		<pattern>
			BACCHUS
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Bacchus is a convenient deity invented by the ancients as an excuse for getting drunk.
			Any questions?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					knowledge
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			BRAHMA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Brahma was he who created the Hindus, who are preserved by Vishnu and destroyed by Siva -- a rather neater division of labor than is found among the deities of some other nations.
			Any questions?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					religion
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			DESCARTES
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Descartes was a famous French philosopher, author of the celebrated dictum, Cogito ergo sum, whereby he was pleased to suppose he demonstrated the reality of human existence.  The dictum might be improved, however, thus:  Cogito cogito ergo cogito sum, or  "I think that I think, therefore I think that I am," as close an approach to certainty as any philosopher has yet made.
			Any questions?
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					philosophy
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
</aiml>
