<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			Q
		</pattern>
		<template>
			q?  Briefly, q means the 17th letter of the Roman alphabet.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			Q FEVER
		</pattern>
		<template>
			q fever?  Briefly, q fever means an acute disease resembling influenza.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QABALA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qabala?  Briefly, qabala means an esoteric or occult matter resembling the Kabbalah that is traditionally secret.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QABALAH
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qabalah?  Briefly, qabalah means an esoteric or occult matter resembling the Kabbalah that is traditionally secret.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QABALISTIC
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qabalistic?  Briefly, qabalistic means having a secret or hidden meaning- John Gunther.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QABBALA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qabbala?  Briefly, qabbala means an esoteric theosophy of rabbinical origin based on the Hebrew scriptures and developed between the 7th and 18th centuries.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QABBALAH
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qabbalah?  Briefly, qabbalah means an esoteric theosophy of rabbinical origin based on the Hebrew scriptures and developed between the 7th and 18th centuries.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QADDAFI
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qaddafi?  Briefly, qaddafi means Libyan leader who seized power in a military coup d'etat in 1969; deposed the Libyan monarchy and imposed socialism and Islamic orthodoxy on the country (born in 1942).
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QADHAFI
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qadhafi?  Briefly, qadhafi means Libyan leader who seized power in a military coup d'etat in 1969; deposed the Libyan monarchy and imposed socialism and Islamic orthodoxy on the country (born in 1942).
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QADI
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qadi?  Briefly, qadi means an Islamic judge.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QAEDA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qaeda?  Briefly, qaeda means an intensely anti-western terrorist network that dispenses money and logistical support and training to a wide variety of radical Islamic terrorist group; has cells in more than 50 countries.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QANDAHAR
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qandahar?  Briefly, qandahar means a city in southern Afghanistan; an important trading center.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QASSAM BRIGADES
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qassam brigades?  Briefly, qassam brigades means the military arm of Hamas responsible for suicide bombings and other attacks on Israel.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QAT
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qat?  Briefly, qat means the leaves of the shrub Catha edulis which are chewed like tobacco or used to make tea; has the effect of a euphoric stimulant.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QATAR
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qatar?  Briefly, qatar means an Arab country on the peninsula of Qatar; achieved independence from the United Kingdom in 1971; the economy is dominated by oil.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QATAR PENINSULA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qatar peninsula?  Briefly, qatar peninsula means a peninsula extending northward from the Arabian mainland into the Persian Gulf.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QATARI
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qatari?  Briefly, qatari means a native or inhabitant of Qatar.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QATARI DIRHAM
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qatari dirham?  Briefly, qatari dirham means 100 dirhams equal 1 riyal.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QATARI MONETARY UNIT
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qatari monetary unit?  Briefly, qatari monetary unit means monetary unit in Qatar.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QATARI RIYAL
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qatari riyal?  Briefly, qatari riyal means the basic unit of money in Qatar.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QCD
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qcd?  Briefly, qcd means a theory of strong interactions between elementary particles (including the interaction that binds protons and neutrons in the nucleus); it assumes that strongly interacting particles (hadrons) are made of quarks and that gluons bind th.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QED
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qed?  Briefly, qed means a relativistic quantum theory of the electromagnetic interactions of photons and electrons and muons.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QEPIQ
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qepiq?  Briefly, qepiq means 100 qepiq equal 1 manat.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QI
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qi?  Briefly, qi means the circulating life energy that in Chinese philosophy is thought to be inherent in all things; in traditional Chinese medicine the balance of negative and positive forms in the body is believed to be essential for good health.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QIANG
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qiang?  Briefly, qiang means the Tibeto-Burman language spoken in Sichuan.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QIANGIC
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qiangic?  Briefly, qiangic means the Tibeto-Burman language spoken in Sichuan.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QIBLA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qibla?  Briefly, qibla means the direction of the Kaaba toward which Muslims turn for their daily prayers.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QINDARKA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qindarka?  Briefly, qindarka means 100 qindarka equal 1 lek.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QING
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qing?  Briefly, qing means the last imperial dynasty of China (from 1644 to 1912) which was overthrown by revolutionaries; during the Qing dynasty China was ruled by the Manchu.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QING DYNASTY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qing dynasty?  Briefly, qing dynasty means the last imperial dynasty of China (from 1644 to 1912) which was overthrown by revolutionaries; during the Qing dynasty China was ruled by the Manchu.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QINTAR
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qintar?  Briefly, qintar means 100 qindarka equal 1 lek.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QOPH
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qoph?  Briefly, qoph means the 19th letter of the Hebrew alphabet.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAALUDE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quaalude?  Briefly, quaalude means sedative-hypnotic drug (trade name Quaalude) that is a drug of abuse.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUACK
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quack?  Briefly, quack means an untrained person who pretends to be a physician and who dispenses medical advice.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUACK GRASS
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quack grass?  Briefly, quack grass means European grass spreading rapidly by creeping rhizomes; naturalized in North America as a weed.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUACKERY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quackery?  Briefly, quackery means medical practice and advice based on observation and experience in ignorance of scientific findings.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUACKGRASS
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quackgrass?  Briefly, quackgrass means European grass spreading rapidly by creeping rhizomes; naturalized in North America as a weed.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUACK-QUACK
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quack-quack?  Briefly, quack-quack means child's word for a duck.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAD
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quad?  Briefly, quad means one of four children born at the same time from the same pregnancy.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRAGESIMA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadragesima?  Briefly, quadragesima means the first Sunday in Lent.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRANGLE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrangle?  Briefly, quadrangle means a four-sided polygon.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRANGULAR
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrangular?  Briefly, quadrangular means of or relating to or shaped like a quadrangle.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRANGULAR PRISM
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrangular prism?  Briefly, quadrangular prism means a prism whose bases are quadrangles.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRANT
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrant?  Briefly, quadrant means a quarter of the circumference of a circle.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRANTANOPIA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrantanopia?  Briefly, quadrantanopia means blindness in one fourth of the visual field.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRAPHONIC
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadraphonic?  Briefly, quadraphonic means of or relating to quadraphony.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRAPHONIC SYSTEM
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadraphonic system?  Briefly, quadraphonic system means a stereophonic sound recording or reproducing system system using four separate channels.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRAPHONY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadraphony?  Briefly, quadraphony means a stereophonic sound recording or reproducing system system using four separate channels.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRASONIC
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrasonic?  Briefly, quadrasonic means of or relating to quadraphony.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRATE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrate?  Briefly, quadrate means a cubelike object.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRATIC
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadratic?  Briefly, quadratic means an equation in which the highest power of an unknown quantity is a square.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRATIC EQUATION
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadratic equation?  Briefly, quadratic equation means an equation in which the highest power of an unknown quantity is a square.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRATIC POLYNOMIAL
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadratic polynomial?  Briefly, quadratic polynomial means a polynomial of the second degree.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRATICS
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadratics?  Briefly, quadratics means a branch of algebra dealing with quadratic equations.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRATURE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrature?  Briefly, quadrature means the construction of a square having the same area as some other figure.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRIC
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadric?  Briefly, quadric means a curve or surface whose equation (in Cartesian coordinates) is of the second degree.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRIC SURFACE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadric surface?  Briefly, quadric surface means a curve or surface whose equation (in Cartesian coordinates) is of the second degree.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRICEPS
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadriceps?  Briefly, quadriceps means a muscle of the thigh that extends the leg.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRICEPS FEMORIS
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadriceps femoris?  Briefly, quadriceps femoris means a muscle of the thigh that extends the leg.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRIGESIMA SUNDAY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrigesima sunday?  Briefly, quadrigesima sunday means the first Sunday in Lent.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRILATERAL
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrilateral?  Briefly, quadrilateral means a four-sided polygon.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRILLE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrille?  Briefly, quadrille means music for dancing the quadrille.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRILLION
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrillion?  Briefly, quadrillion means the number that is represented as a one followed by 24 zeros.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRILLIONTH
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrillionth?  Briefly, quadrillionth means one part in a quadrillion.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRIPARA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadripara?  Briefly, quadripara means woman who has given birth to a viable infant in each of four pregnancies.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRIPARTITE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadripartite?  Briefly, quadripartite means involving four parties.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRIPHONIC
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadriphonic?  Briefly, quadriphonic means of or relating to quadraphony.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRIPHONIC SYSTEM
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadriphonic system?  Briefly, quadriphonic system means a stereophonic sound recording or reproducing system system using four separate channels.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRIPLEGIA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadriplegia?  Briefly, quadriplegia means paralysis of both arms and both legs.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRIPLEGIC
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadriplegic?  Briefly, quadriplegic means a person who is paralyzed in both arms and both legs.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRISONIC
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrisonic?  Briefly, quadrisonic means of or relating to quadraphony.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADROON
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadroon?  Briefly, quadroon means an offspring of a Mulatto and a White parent; a person who is one-quarter Black.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRUMVIRATE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrumvirate?  Briefly, quadrumvirate means a group of four men.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRUPED
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadruped?  Briefly, quadruped means an animal especially a mammal having four limbs specialized for walking.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRUPEDAL
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrupedal?  Briefly, quadrupedal means having four feet.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRUPLE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadruple?  Briefly, quadruple means a quantity that is four times as great as another.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRUPLE TIME
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadruple time?  Briefly, quadruple time means a time signature indicating four beats to the bar.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRUPLET
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadruplet?  Briefly, quadruplet means the cardinal number that is the sum of three and one.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRUPLEX
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadruplex?  Briefly, quadruplex means having four units or components.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRUPLICATE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadruplicate?  Briefly, quadruplicate means any four copies; any of four things that correspond to one another exactly.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUADRUPLING
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quadrupling?  Briefly, quadrupling means increase by a factor of four.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAESTOR
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quaestor?  Briefly, quaestor means any of several public officials of ancient Rome (usually in charge of finance and administration).
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAFF
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quaff?  Briefly, quaff means a hearty draft.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAFFER
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quaffer?  Briefly, quaffer means a person who drinks heartily.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAG
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quag?  Briefly, quag means a soft wet area of low-lying land that sinks underfoot.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAGGA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quagga?  Briefly, quagga means mammal of South Africa that resembled a zebra; extinct since late 19th century.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAGGY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quaggy?  Briefly, quaggy means soft and watery.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAGMIRE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quagmire?  Briefly, quagmire means a soft wet area of low-lying land that sinks underfoot.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAHAUG
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quahaug?  Briefly, quahaug means Atlantic coast round clams with hard shells; large clams usually used for chowders or other clam dishes.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAHOG
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quahog?  Briefly, quahog means Atlantic coast round clams with hard shells; large clams usually used for chowders or other clam dishes.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAI D'ORSAY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quai d'orsay?  Briefly, quai d'orsay means the street in Paris along the south bank of the Seine known for its governmental ministries.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAIL
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quail?  Briefly, quail means flesh of quail; suitable for roasting or broiling if young; otherwise must be braised.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAIL AT
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quail at?  Briefly, quail at means anticipate with dread or anxiety.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAIL BRUSH
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quail brush?  Briefly, quail brush means spiny shrub with silvery-scurfy foliage of alkaline plains of southwestern United States and Mexico.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAIL BUSH
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quail bush?  Briefly, quail bush means spiny shrub with silvery-scurfy foliage of alkaline plains of southwestern United States and Mexico.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAINT
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quaint?  Briefly, quaint means strange in an interesting or pleasing way.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAINTLY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quaintly?  Briefly, quaintly means in a strange but not unpleasant manner.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAINTNESS
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quaintness?  Briefly, quaintness means the quality of being quaint and old-fashioned.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAKE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quake?  Briefly, quake means shaking and vibration at the surface of the earth resulting from underground movement along a fault plane of from volcanic activity.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAKER
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quaker?  Briefly, quaker means a member of the Religious Society of Friends founded by George Fox (the Friends have never called themselves Quakers).
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAKER GUN
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quaker gun?  Briefly, quaker gun means a dummy gun or piece of artillery made usually of wood.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAKERISM
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quakerism?  Briefly, quakerism means the theological doctrine of the Society of Friends characterized by opposition to war and rejection of ritual and a formal creed and an ordained ministry.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAKERS
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quakers?  Briefly, quakers means a Christian sect founded by George Fox about 1660; commonly called Quakers.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAKING
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quaking?  Briefly, quaking means vibrating slightly and irregularly; as e.g. with fear or cold or like the leaves of an aspen in a breeze.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAKING ASPEN
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quaking aspen?  Briefly, quaking aspen means Old World aspen with a broad much-branched crown; northwestern Europe and Siberia to North Africa.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUALIFICATION
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qualification?  Briefly, qualification means an attribute that must be met or complied with and that fits a person for something.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUALIFIED
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qualified?  Briefly, qualified means meeting the proper standards and requirements and training for an office or position or task.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUALIFIER
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qualifier?  Briefly, qualifier means a contestant who meets certain requirements and so qualifies to take part in the next stage of competition.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUALIFY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qualify?  Briefly, qualify means prove capable or fit; meet requirements.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUALIFYING
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qualifying?  Briefly, qualifying means the grammatical relation that exists when a word qualifies the meaning of the phrase.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUALIFYING ADJECTIVE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qualifying adjective?  Briefly, qualifying adjective means an adjective that ascribes to its noun the value of an attribute of that noun (e.g. means `a nervous person' or `a musical speaking voice').
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUALITATIVE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qualitative?  Briefly, qualitative means involving distinctions based on qualities.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUALITATIVE ANALYSIS
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qualitative analysis?  Briefly, qualitative analysis means the act of decomposing a substance into its constituent elements.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUALITATIVELY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qualitatively?  Briefly, qualitatively means in a qualitative manner.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUALITY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quality?  Briefly, quality means an essential and distinguishing attribute of something or someone--Shakespeare.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUALITY CONTROL
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quality control?  Briefly, quality control means maintenance of standards of quality of manufactured goods.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUALITY OF LIFE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quality of life?  Briefly, quality of life means your personal satisfaction (or dissatisfaction) with the cultural or intellectual conditions under which you live (as distinct from material comfort).
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUALM
		</pattern>
		<template>
			qualm?  Briefly, qualm means uneasiness about the fitness of an action.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAMASH
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quamash?  Briefly, quamash means any of several plants of the genus Camassia; North and South America.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAMASSIA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quamassia?  Briefly, quamassia means genus of scapose herbs of North and South America having large edible bulbs.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUAMOCLIT PENNATA
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quamoclit pennata?  Briefly, quamoclit pennata means tropical American annual climber having red (sometimes white) flowers and finely dissected leaves; naturalized in United States and elsewhere.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANDANG
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quandang?  Briefly, quandang means Australian tree with edible flesh and edible nutlike seed.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANDARY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quandary?  Briefly, quandary means a situation from which extrication is difficult especially an unpleasant or trying one.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANDONG
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quandong?  Briefly, quandong means Australian tree with edible flesh and edible nutlike seed.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANDONG NUT
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quandong nut?  Briefly, quandong nut means edible nutlike seed of the quandong fruit.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANDONG TREE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quandong tree?  Briefly, quandong tree means Australian tree with edible flesh and edible nutlike seed.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANGO
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quango?  Briefly, quango means QUAsi Non-Governmental Organization; an organization that is financed by the government yet acts independently of the government.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTAL
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantal?  Briefly, quantal means of or relating to a quantum or capable of existing in only one of two states.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTIFIABILITY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantifiability?  Briefly, quantifiability means the quality of being measurable.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTIFIABLE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantifiable?  Briefly, quantifiable means capable of being quantified.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTIFICATION
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantification?  Briefly, quantification means a limitation imposed on the variables of a proposition (as by the quantifiers `some' or `all' or `no').
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTIFIER
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantifier?  Briefly, quantifier means a word (such as `some' or `all' or `no') that binds the variables in a logical proposition.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTIFY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantify?  Briefly, quantify means use as a quantifier.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTISATION
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantisation?  Briefly, quantisation means the act of dividing into quanta or expressing in terms of quantum theory.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTISE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantise?  Briefly, quantise means telecommunications: approximate (a signal varying continuously in amplitude) by one whose amplitude is restricted to a prescribed set of discrete values.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTITATIVE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantitative?  Briefly, quantitative means expressible as a quantity or relating to or susceptible of measurement.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTITATIVE ANALYSIS
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantitative analysis?  Briefly, quantitative analysis means chemical analysis to determine the amounts of each element in the substance.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTITATIVE CHEMICAL ANALYSIS
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantitative chemical analysis?  Briefly, quantitative chemical analysis means chemical analysis to determine the amounts of each element in the substance.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTITATIVE RELATION
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantitative relation?  Briefly, quantitative relation means a relation between magnitudes.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTITATIVELY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantitatively?  Briefly, quantitatively means in a quantitative manner.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTITY
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantity?  Briefly, quantity means how much there is of something that you can quantify.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTITY UNIT
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantity unit?  Briefly, quantity unit means a measure of the quantity of electricity (determined by the amount of an electric current and the time for which it flows).
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTIZATION
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantization?  Briefly, quantization means the act of dividing into quanta or expressing in terms of quantum theory.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTIZE
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantize?  Briefly, quantize means telecommunications: approximate (a signal varying continuously in amplitude) by one whose amplitude is restricted to a prescribed set of discrete values.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTIZED
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantized?  Briefly, quantized means of or relating to a quantum or capable of existing in only one of two states.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTONG
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantong?  Briefly, quantong means red Australian fruit; used for dessert or in jam.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUANTUM
		</pattern>
		<template>
			quantum?  Briefly, quantum means a discrete amount of something that is analogous to the quantum in quantum theory.
		</template>
	</category>
	
	<category><pattern>QUARK</pattern>
	<template>In physics, a quark is a subatomic particle below the level of electrons and protons. There are six different types of quark.
	<think><set name="topic">science</set></think></template></category>
	
	
	<category><pattern>QUASAR</pattern>
	<template>A quasar is a celestial  star-like object that has a large red shift and radiates in the blue and radio bands of the electromagnetic spectrum.  The term 'quasar' is a shortening of 'quasi-star'. More astronomy?
	<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think></template></category>
	
	
	<category><pattern>QUERY</pattern>
	<template>A query is any expression of inquiry, or questioning.  Your question 'what is a query' is a query.
	<think><set name="topic">general</set></think></template></category>
	
	
	<category><pattern>QUESTION</pattern>
	<template>
	A question is a sentence or inquiry to gather information.
	<think><set name="topic">general</set></think></template></category>
	
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUASH *
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Quash must mean quince cordial, I think.
			<think>
				<set name="topic">
					food
				</set>
			</think>
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			*
			QUIET
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Quiet is a state of household serenity which occurs before the birth of the first child and occurs again after the last child has left for college.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUIET *
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Quiet is a state of household serenity which occurs before the birth of the first child and occurs again after the last child has left for college.
		</template>
	</category>
	<category>
		<pattern>
			QUIET
		</pattern>
		<template>
			Quiet is a state of household serenity which occurs before the birth of the first child and occurs again after the last child has left for college.
		</template>
	</category>
</aiml>
