<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>

<category><pattern>B</pattern> 
    <template> 
        <random>
            <li><srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  b <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  is the second letter of the English alphabet.</li>
        </random>
    </template>
</category>
<category><pattern>Q</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  q <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the 17th letter of the Roman alphabet.</template></category>
<category><pattern>Q FEVER</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  q fever <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an acute disease resembling influenza.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QABALA</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qabala <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an esoteric or occult matter resembling the Kabbalah that is traditionally secret.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QABALAH</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qabalah <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an esoteric or occult matter resembling the Kabbalah that is traditionally secret.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QABALISTIC</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qabalistic <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  having a secret or hidden meaning- John Gunther.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QABBALA</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qabbala <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an esoteric theosophy of rabbinical origin based on the Hebrew scriptures and developed between the 7th and 18th centuries.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QABBALAH</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qabbalah <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an esoteric theosophy of rabbinical origin based on the Hebrew scriptures and developed between the 7th and 18th centuries.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QADDAFI</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qaddafi <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  Libyan leader who seized power in a military coup d'etat in 1969; deposed the Libyan monarchy and imposed socialism and Islamic orthodoxy on the country (born in 1942).</template></category>
<category><pattern>QADHAFI</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qadhafi <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  Libyan leader who seized power in a military coup d'etat in 1969; deposed the Libyan monarchy and imposed socialism and Islamic orthodoxy on the country (born in 1942).</template></category>
<category><pattern>QADI</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qadi <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an Islamic judge.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QAEDA</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qaeda <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an intensely anti-western terrorist network that dispenses money and logistical support and training to a wide variety of radical Islamic terrorist group; has cells in more than 50 countries.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QANDAHAR</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qandahar <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a city in southern Afghanistan; an important trading center.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QASSAM BRIGADES</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qassam brigades <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the military arm of Hamas responsible for suicide bombings and other attacks on Israel.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QAT</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qat <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the leaves of the shrub Catha edulis which are chewed like tobacco or used to make tea; has the effect of a euphoric stimulant.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QATAR</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qatar <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an Arab country on the peninsula of Qatar; achieved independence from the United Kingdom in 1971; the economy is dominated by oil.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QATAR PENINSULA</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qatar peninsula <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a peninsula extending northward from the Arabian mainland into the Persian Gulf.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QATARI</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qatari <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a native or inhabitant of Qatar.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QATARI DIRHAM</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qatari dirham <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  100 dirhams equal 1 riyal.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QATARI MONETARY UNIT</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qatari monetary unit <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  monetary unit in Qatar.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QATARI RIYAL</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qatari riyal <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the basic unit of money in Qatar.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QCD</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qcd <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a theory of strong interactions between elementary particles (including the interaction that binds protons and neutrons in the nucleus); it assumes that strongly interacting particles (hadrons) are made of quarks and that gluons bind th.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QED</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qed <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a relativistic quantum theory of the electromagnetic interactions of photons and electrons and muons.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QEPIQ</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qepiq <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  100 qepiq equal 1 manat.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QI</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qi <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the circulating life energy that in Chinese philosophy is thought to be inherent in all things; in traditional Chinese medicine the balance of negative and positive forms in the body is believed to be essential for good health.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QIANG</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qiang <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the Tibeto-Burman language spoken in Sichuan.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QIANGIC</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qiangic <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the Tibeto-Burman language spoken in Sichuan.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QIBLA</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qibla <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the direction of the Kaaba toward which Muslims turn for their daily prayers.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QINDARKA</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qindarka <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  100 qindarka equal 1 lek.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QING</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qing <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the last imperial dynasty of China (from 1644 to 1912) which was overthrown by revolutionaries; during the Qing dynasty China was ruled by the Manchu.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QING DYNASTY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qing dynasty <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the last imperial dynasty of China (from 1644 to 1912) which was overthrown by revolutionaries; during the Qing dynasty China was ruled by the Manchu.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QINTAR</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qintar <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  100 qindarka equal 1 lek.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QOPH</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qoph <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the 19th letter of the Hebrew alphabet.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAALUDE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quaalude <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  sedative-hypnotic drug (trade name Quaalude) that is a drug of abuse.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUACK</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quack <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an untrained person who pretends to be a physician and who dispenses medical advice.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUACK GRASS</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quack grass <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  European grass spreading rapidly by creeping rhizomes; naturalized in North America as a weed.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUACK-QUACK</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quack-quack <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  child's word for a duck.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUACKERY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quackery <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  medical practice and advice based on observation and experience in ignorance of scientific findings.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUACKGRASS</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quackgrass <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  European grass spreading rapidly by creeping rhizomes; naturalized in North America as a weed.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAD</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quad <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  one of four children born at the same time from the same pregnancy.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRAGESIMA</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadragesima <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the first Sunday in Lent.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRANGLE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrangle <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a four-sided polygon.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRANGULAR</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrangular <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  of or relating to or shaped like a quadrangle.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRANGULAR PRISM</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrangular prism <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a prism whose bases are quadrangles.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRANT</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrant <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a quarter of the circumference of a circle.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRANTANOPIA</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrantanopia <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  blindness in one fourth of the visual field.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRAPHONIC</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadraphonic <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  of or relating to quadraphony.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRAPHONIC SYSTEM</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadraphonic system <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a stereophonic sound recording or reproducing system system using four separate channels.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRAPHONY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadraphony <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a stereophonic sound recording or reproducing system system using four separate channels.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRASONIC</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrasonic <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  of or relating to quadraphony.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRATE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrate <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a cubelike object.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRATIC</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadratic <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an equation in which the highest power of an unknown quantity is a square.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRATIC EQUATION</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadratic equation <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an equation in which the highest power of an unknown quantity is a square.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRATIC POLYNOMIAL</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadratic polynomial <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a polynomial of the second degree.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRATICS</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadratics <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a branch of algebra dealing with quadratic equations.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRATURE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrature <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the construction of a square having the same area as some other figure.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRIC</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadric <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a curve or surface whose equation (in Cartesian coordinates) is of the second degree.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRIC SURFACE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadric surface <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a curve or surface whose equation (in Cartesian coordinates) is of the second degree.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRICEPS</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadriceps <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a muscle of the thigh that extends the leg.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRICEPS FEMORIS</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadriceps femoris <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a muscle of the thigh that extends the leg.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRIGESIMA SUNDAY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrigesima sunday <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the first Sunday in Lent.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRILATERAL</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrilateral <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a four-sided polygon.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRILLE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrille <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  music for dancing the quadrille.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRILLION</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrillion <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the number that is represented as a one followed by 24 zeros.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRILLIONTH</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrillionth <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  one part in a quadrillion.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRIPARA</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadripara <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  woman who has given birth to a viable infant in each of four pregnancies.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRIPARTITE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadripartite <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  involving four parties.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRIPHONIC</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadriphonic <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  of or relating to quadraphony.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRIPHONIC SYSTEM</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadriphonic system <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a stereophonic sound recording or reproducing system system using four separate channels.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRIPLEGIA</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadriplegia <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  paralysis of both arms and both legs.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRIPLEGIC</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadriplegic <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a person who is paralyzed in both arms and both legs.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRISONIC</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrisonic <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  of or relating to quadraphony.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADROON</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadroon <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an offspring of a Mulatto and a White parent; a person who is one-quarter Black.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRUMVIRATE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrumvirate <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a group of four men.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRUPED</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadruped <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an animal especially a mammal having four limbs specialized for walking.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRUPEDAL</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrupedal <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  having four feet.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRUPLE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadruple <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a quantity that is four times as great as another.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRUPLE TIME</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadruple time <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a time signature indicating four beats to the bar.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRUPLET</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadruplet <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the cardinal number that is the sum of three and one.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRUPLEX</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadruplex <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  having four units or components.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRUPLICATE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadruplicate <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  any four copies; any of four things that correspond to one another exactly.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUADRUPLING</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quadrupling <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  increase by a factor of four.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAESTOR</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quaestor <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  any of several public officials of ancient Rome (usually in charge of finance and administration).</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAFF</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quaff <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a hearty draft.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAFFER</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quaffer <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a person who drinks heartily.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAG</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quag <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a soft wet area of low-lying land that sinks underfoot.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAGGA</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quagga <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  mammal of South Africa that resembled a zebra; extinct since late 19th century.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAGGY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quaggy <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  soft and watery.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAGMIRE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quagmire <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a soft wet area of low-lying land that sinks underfoot.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAHAUG</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quahaug <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  Atlantic coast round clams with hard shells; large clams usually used for chowders or other clam dishes.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAHOG</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quahog <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  Atlantic coast round clams with hard shells; large clams usually used for chowders or other clam dishes.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAI D'ORSAY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quai d'orsay <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the street in Paris along the south bank of the Seine known for its governmental ministries.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAIL</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quail <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  flesh of quail; suitable for roasting or broiling if young; otherwise must be braised.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAIL AT</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quail at <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  anticipate with dread or anxiety.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAIL BRUSH</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quail brush <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  spiny shrub with silvery-scurfy foliage of alkaline plains of southwestern United States and Mexico.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAIL BUSH</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quail bush <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  spiny shrub with silvery-scurfy foliage of alkaline plains of southwestern United States and Mexico.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAINT</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quaint <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  strange in an interesting or pleasing way.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAINTLY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quaintly <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  in a strange but not unpleasant manner.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAINTNESS</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quaintness <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the quality of being quaint and old-fashioned.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAKE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quake <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  shaking and vibration at the surface of the earth resulting from underground movement along a fault plane of from volcanic activity.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAKER</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quaker <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a member of the Religious Society of Friends founded by George Fox (the Friends have never called themselves Quakers).</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAKER GUN</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quaker gun <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a dummy gun or piece of artillery made usually of wood.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAKERISM</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quakerism <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the theological doctrine of the Society of Friends characterized by opposition to war and rejection of ritual and a formal creed and an ordained ministry.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAKERS</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quakers <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a Christian sect founded by George Fox about 1660; commonly called Quakers.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAKING</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quaking <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  vibrating slightly and irregularly; as e.g. with fear or cold or like the leaves of an aspen in a breeze.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAKING ASPEN</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quaking aspen <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  Old World aspen with a broad much-branched crown; northwestern Europe and Siberia to North Africa.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUALIFICATION</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qualification <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an attribute that must be met or complied with and that fits a person for something.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUALIFIED</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qualified <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  meeting the proper standards and requirements and training for an office or position or task.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUALIFIER</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qualifier <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a contestant who meets certain requirements and so qualifies to take part in the next stage of competition.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUALIFY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qualify <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  prove capable or fit; meet requirements.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUALIFYING</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qualifying <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the grammatical relation that exists when a word qualifies the meaning of the phrase.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUALIFYING ADJECTIVE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qualifying adjective <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an adjective that ascribes to its noun the value of an attribute of that noun (e.g. <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  `a nervous person' or `a musical speaking voice').</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUALITATIVE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qualitative <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  involving distinctions based on qualities.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUALITATIVE ANALYSIS</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qualitative analysis <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the act of decomposing a substance into its constituent elements.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUALITATIVELY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qualitatively <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  in a qualitative manner.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUALITY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quality <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  an essential and distinguishing attribute of something or someone--Shakespeare.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUALITY CONTROL</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quality control <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  maintenance of standards of quality of manufactured goods.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUALITY OF LIFE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quality of life <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  your personal satisfaction (or dissatisfaction) with the cultural or intellectual conditions under which you live (as distinct from material comfort).</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUALM</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  qualm <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  uneasiness about the fitness of an action.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAMASH</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quamash <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  any of several plants of the genus Camassia; North and South America.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAMASSIA</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quamassia <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  genus of scapose herbs of North and South America having large edible bulbs.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUAMOCLIT PENNATA</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quamoclit pennata <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  tropical American annual climber having red (sometimes white) flowers and finely dissected leaves; naturalized in United States and elsewhere.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANDANG</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quandang <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  Australian tree with edible flesh and edible nutlike seed.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANDARY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quandary <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a situation from which extrication is difficult especially an unpleasant or trying one.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANDONG</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quandong <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  Australian tree with edible flesh and edible nutlike seed.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANDONG NUT</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quandong nut <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  edible nutlike seed of the quandong fruit.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANDONG TREE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quandong tree <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  Australian tree with edible flesh and edible nutlike seed.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANGO</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quango <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  QUAsi Non-Governmental Organization; an organization that is financed by the government yet acts independently of the government.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTAL</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantal <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  of or relating to a quantum or capable of existing in only one of two states.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTIFIABILITY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantifiability <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the quality of being measurable.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTIFIABLE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantifiable <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  capable of being quantified.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTIFICATION</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantification <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a limitation imposed on the variables of a proposition (as by the quantifiers `some' or `all' or `no').</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTIFIER</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantifier <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a word (such as `some' or `all' or `no') that binds the variables in a logical proposition.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTIFY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantify <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  use as a quantifier.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTISATION</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantisation <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the act of dividing into quanta or expressing in terms of quantum theory.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTISE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantise <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  telecommunications: approximate (a signal varying continuously in amplitude) by one whose amplitude is restricted to a prescribed set of discrete values.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTITATIVE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantitative <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  expressible as a quantity or relating to or susceptible of measurement.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTITATIVE ANALYSIS</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantitative analysis <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  chemical analysis to determine the amounts of each element in the substance.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTITATIVE CHEMICAL ANALYSIS</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantitative chemical analysis <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  chemical analysis to determine the amounts of each element in the substance.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTITATIVE RELATION</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantitative relation <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a relation between magnitudes.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTITATIVELY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantitatively <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  in a quantitative manner.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTITY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantity <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  how much there is of something that you can quantify.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTITY UNIT</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantity unit <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a measure of the quantity of electricity (determined by the amount of an electric current and the time for which it flows).</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTIZATION</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantization <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  the act of dividing into quanta or expressing in terms of quantum theory.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTIZE</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantize <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  telecommunications: approximate (a signal varying continuously in amplitude) by one whose amplitude is restricted to a prescribed set of discrete values.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTIZED</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantized <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  of or relating to a quantum or capable of existing in only one of two states.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTONG</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantong <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  red Australian fruit; used for dessert or in jam.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUANTUM</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai>  quantum <srai>DEFINITION MEANS</srai>  a discrete amount of something that is analogous to the quantum in quantum theory.</template></category>
<category><pattern>QUARK</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai> In physics, a quark is a subatomic particle below the level of electrons and protons. There are six different types of quark.<think><set name="topic">science</set></think></template></category>
<category><pattern>QUASAR</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai> A quasar is a celestial star-like object that has a large red shift and radiates in the blue and radio bands of the electromagnetic spectrum. The term 'quasar' is a shortening of 'quasi-star'. More astronomy?<think><set name="topic">astronomy</set></think></template></category>
<category><pattern>QUASH *</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai> Quash must mean quince cordial, I think.<think><set name="topic">food</set></think></template></category>
<category><pattern>QUERY</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai> A query is any expression of inquiry, or questioning. Your question 'what is a query' is a query.<think><set name="topic">general</set></think></template></category>
<category><pattern>QUESTION</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai> A question is a sentence or inquiry to gather information.<think><set name="topic">general</set></think></template></category>
<category><pattern>* QUIET</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai> Quiet is a state of household serenity which occurs before the birth of the first child and occurs again after the last child has left for college.</template></category>
DUPLICATE: <category><pattern>QUIET *</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai> Quiet is a state of household serenity which occurs before the birth of the first child and occurs again after the last child has left for college.</template></category>
DUPLICATE: <category><pattern>QUIET</pattern> <template> <srai>DEFINITION START</srai> Quiet is a state of household serenity which occurs before the birth of the first child and occurs again after the last child has left for college.</template></category>

</aiml>
